制作人：gemini0421  来源：人人影视
{\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HCE8F00&\t(4500,5000,1,\fry360)\move(74,198,62,226,4500,5000)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
{\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HF6DBA1&\t(4500,5000,1,\fry360)\move(74,198,62,226,4500,5000)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
{\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx15\fscy18\p1\1a&H3D&\c&HFFFFFF&\blur10\move(64,188,51,218,4500,5000)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
{\fad(500,500)\blur20\bord0\shad0\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HECB000&\pos(90,198)\t(0,1000,1,\blur0)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
{\fad(500,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\b1\c&HFFFFFF&\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\c&HECB000&\pos(105,215)\clip(50,154,52,223)\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,154,335,225))}原创翻译 双语字幕
{\clip(50,154,52,223)\fad(500,500)\3c&HFFFFFF&\fscx600\fs86\alpha&H9F&\c&H000000&\bord1\shad0\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,154,335,225))\pos(192,234)}■
{\fad(500,500)\fs16\fn方正准圆简体\b1\bord0\shad0\pos(237,215)\clip(50,154,52,223)\t(0,1000,1,\clip(52,154,335,225))}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
x1080)}翻译：大卫熊  Silence  点点点  欧阳  胖兔纯
x1080)}翻译：王大可  圈圈  H小欠  卫老哥  爱卿遛小鸟
rx1080)}时间轴：雪贵人  JimmyBeck   校对：米小勒  大卫熊
{\an5\fad(500,500)\fs16\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正准圆简体\shad0\bord1\blur5\clip(73,192,361,228)\move(-40,210,200,210,0,500)\t(4500,5000,1,\frx1080)}后期：瓜瓜     总监：米小勒
{\fs20\3c&HFFFFFF&\fs36\fscx1450\alpha&H9F&\c&H000000&\bord1\shad0\clip(71,192,75,230)\t(0,500,1,\clip(73,192,361,228)\t(20000,20500,1,\clip(71,192,75,230)))\pos(206,229)}■
漫威公司出品
神盾局特工
第一季 第七集
我不想让你们很惊慌
I don't mean to alarm you,
不过我认为你们这里不卫生  都发霉了
but I think you may have a mold problem.
水池里的积水让人尤其担忧
That sink with the standing water seems especially concerning.
等审讯官来
他就笑不出来了
我很期待呢
Looking forward to it.
情报在你身上吗
You have the intel on you?
他们知道了
They know.
是吗
They know?
我们只有三分钟  肖特工
We have three minutes, Agent Shaw.
该走了  肖特工
Time to go, Agent Shaw.
-从哪撤  -跟着我
- Exit? - Follow me.
我刚在想你们在搞什么名堂
I was wondering what you guys had been up to.
你先上
Go.
好
All right.
雪橇狗在哪
Um, where are the dogs?
别逗了  用不着
Don't be ridiculous.
通常情况下  我敢说是你拿着这种东西
I bet you're usually the one holding something like this.
别担心
Don't worry.
她知道自己在干什么
She knows what she's doing.
不要呼吸哦
Whatever you do, don't breathe.
开玩笑啦
That was a joke.
你当然可以呼吸  如果你觉得需要的话
You should, of course, feel comfortable breathing if you need to,
别用鼻子就行
Just not through your nose.
用嘴呼吸也要幅度很小
And very minimally through your mouth.
拿到了
There we are.
这是你获取的所有情报吗
That's all the intel you recovered?
我当然希望是
I certainly hope so.
谢谢你  肖特工
Well, thank you, Agent Shaw,
安全地保管情报
for keeping it safe up there.
我们会把它送回中心
We'll push this through to the Hub.
事实上  我们正开往那里  把你留在那
In fact, we're headed there now to drop you off.
换套衣服  吃顿像样的饭
Get you a change of clothes, a proper meal --
你会马上调整好状态的
You'll be good as new.
中心  真的吗
The Hub? Really?
好激动  好久没去了
How exciting. It's been ages.
很好
Good.
鼻旁取出已经完成了
Done with that paranasal extraction nonsense.
你需要我来分析这数据吗
Do you need me to analyze the data?
不必
That won't be necessary.
如果加密了  我可以帮他搞定芯片
If it's encrypted, I can mine the chip for him.
恐怕这个任务是机密的
I'm afraid this mission's classified.
权限等级8
Clearance level 8.
等等  什么
Wait. What?
他一句话就可以让我们不闻不问吗
He can just shut us out of the process like that?
他说过任务是等级8了
Well, he did say the mission is level 8.
我们没那权限  所以我们没法知道
And we're not, so we can't know about it.
但这通常是
Right, but this is normally the part
我们围站在操作台前  获取情报的时候
where we all stand around the holocom and we learn about stuff.
我是说  我们是一伙儿的  不是吗
I mean, aren't we all on the same team?
用不着搞你那套社会主义理论了
No need to get started on one of your socialist riffs.
神盾局的基础结构是基于等级制度
S.H.I.E.L.D.'s whole infrastructure is based on the hierarchy
和情报的等级划分
and compartmentalization of intelligence.
每个任务的情报不能让每个特工都知道
Every agent can't have the intel on every mission.
那会让整个组织变得很脆弱
Makes the entire organization vulnerable.
好吧  但是如果我刚从
Okay, fine, but if I just fought my way out
西伯利亚的地下监狱逃出
of an underground Siberian prison,
我会希望知道行动是为了什么
I'd kind of want to know what for.
科尔森让你习惯了飞机上的套路
Coulson's got you used to the plane,
我们在这里行动的方式
The way we do missions here.
中心的工作方式可完全不同
The Hub is different.
中心
The Hub?
中心是什么
What's the Hub?
中心
地点: 机密
没想到大本营有这么大
Didn't realize big brother was this big.
这不算什么
Oh, this is nothing.
等你看到三叉戟总部时  那才叫大呢
wait until you see the Triskelion.
所有人都穿同样的服装
Everyone's wearing the same suit.
谁能告诉我为什么
Someone tell me why, please.
有我的吗
Do I get one?
那是你的"胸章"
That's your badge,
意味着你即便要想达到等级1  还有很长的路要走
which means you've got a long way to go to even make level one.
收到
Copy that.
这是不是意味着我不能用这里的任何一台电脑
Does that also mean no access to any computers here whatsoever?
我可以查神盾局关于我父母那个编辑过的档案
I could run a search on the redacted S.H.I.E.L.D. file on my parents.
斯凯
Skye.
但...
But it just --
这里看起来就像是他们被关着的地方
It seems like the place they'd keep them, right?
我会调查的
I'll look into it.
但现在  我们手头上有更紧迫的事情
But right now, we've got more pressing matters at hand.
西特韦尔特工
Agent Sitwell.
科尔森特工
Agent Coulson.
很高兴看到你好转了
Good to see you feeling better.
汉德特工在局势分析室里等你
Agent Hand's waiting for you in the situation room.
她不太喜欢等人
And she doesn't like to wait.
你认识她吗
So you know her?
只是听说过
Only her reputation.
你先请
After you.
你的七级特工可以来简报室里一起听
Your level 7s can join us in the briefing.
笑一个
Say cheese.
维多利亚・汉德
Victoria Hand...
在这里
Is here.
你用这么精妙的方法告诉我不能跟过去吗
Is this your subtle way of saying I can't come with?
我们马上回来
We'll be back.
什
Wha--
我们应该去一下技术走廊了
We should probably head over to the tech corridor.
-我迫不及待想看新化学装备了  -是啊
- Oh, I can't wait to see the new chem-kit. -Yeah
这地方肯定不喜欢我
I don't think it likes me here.
汉德特工
Agent Hand.
科尔森特工
Agent Coulson.
很高兴终于见到你本人了
Nice to finally put a face to the name.
彼此彼此
Likewise.
这是梅特工和沃德特工
These are agents May and Ward.
介绍就到此为止吧
Well, now that we've gotten that over with,
这是你们所能掌握的情报
Here's what you can know.
你们从肖特工手上得到的情报
The intel you recovered from agent Shaw
告诉我们一个南奥塞梯的独立组织
tells us that a separatist group from South Ossetia
制造了一件叫做"艾斯比图米特"的武器
has built a weapon called Ezbiitometer.
是一种超强杀伤性装置吗
The overkill device?
以我的口味看  略显做作
A little dramatic for my taste.
我想可能是名字在翻译过程中遗漏了什么
I imagine something was lost in translation.
我们从拦截到的信号中得知
We've intercepted chatter that tells us
他们打算在接下来的24小时内靠这武器
they plan to use the weapon in the next 24 hours
宣布从俄罗斯和格鲁吉亚那里独立
to declare their independence from Russia and Georgia.
我们认为它会引起音波振动
We believe it creates sonic vibrations
其威力足以在远距离触发武器
Powerful enough to trigger weapons from a great distance --
从直升机上的导弹
Anything from the missiles on a helicopter
到发射井中的核弹头都能触发
To a nuclear warhead sitting in its silo.
所以如果我们对他们动武
So if we move on them,
他们就用我们的武器来对付我们
They could use our own weapons against us.
没错
Exactly.
所以我需要一支二人小队
That's why I need a two-man team
偷偷穿过争议边界
to sneak across the disputed border undetected,
闯进独立组织的要塞
break into the separatist stronghold,
在24小时内让这武器瘫痪
and disable the weapon in the next 24 hours.
而你正好有两个人适合这工作
And you have two people who fit my bill.
没问题
Not a problem.
我参与过08年的格鲁吉亚战争
I was in Georgia during the incursion in '08.
我现在仍与南奥塞梯的边境有联系
I still have contacts on the South Ossetian border.
你们到时必须要操作它们
And you'll have to use them.
但我们没有那仪器方面的专家
But we don't have specs on the device,
所以我需要你们团队中
so I need someone on the team
一个可以到现场识别出并拆除它的人
who can identify and dismantle it on-site.
你的意思是...
Do you mean...
我想就是那意思
I think she does.
我找到一个小范围电磁脉冲
I found a localized E.M.P.,
还有一些其他工具
plus a few other party favors.
拜托  这
Oh, come on. What the...
开门啊
Open.
卡住了
It's stuck!
小车被卡住了
The cart's stuck.
太难以置信了
That's unbelievable.
这什么情况啊
What the hell?!
谁设计的
Who designed this?!
在中心到处都是
In the hub, of all places.
这...
Oh, that's...
你没开玩笑吧
Seriously?
我只是无法想象你要参与
I just can't believe you're going in
那里漆黑一片
dark,
又是敌方领土  不带通讯工具
in hostile territory, without comms,
而你手无缚鸡之力
lacking any real physical strength.
我不会有事的
I'll be fine.
抗蛇毒素我给你了吗
Did I give you an antivenin pack?
高加索有很多当地独有的蜘蛛物种
The caucasus have a plethora of highly endemic spider species.
珍玛  别  别再替我担心了
Jemma, stop. Stop worrying about me.
我没问题的
I can do this.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不在的时候你不要做什么傻事
And don't you do anything rash while I'm gone...
比如说从飞机上跳下去什么的
...like jump out of an airplane.
你要小心
Well, you'll be careful.
更糟糕的情况我都处理过
Yeah, I've handled worse.
差点忘了  我给你做了这个
Oh, I almost forgot. I made you this.
你最爱的三明治
Your favorite sandwich.
意式熏火腿加水牛芝士
Prosciutto and buffalo mozzarella.
加你自制的蒜泥蛋黄酱了吗
With your homemade pesto aioli?
加了一点
Just a hint.
你要的是这个吗
Hey, is this what you wanted?
还有  这是什么
Also, what is this?
菲兹
Oh, Fitz.
全尺寸的弹匣袋
A full-sized mag pouch?
只是我必须做出的一个战术决策而已
Just one of the many tactical decisions I've had to make already.
是沃德说我们需要这个的
And Ward said we needed it.
你们得在明早六点之前解除这个大杀伤力武器
You need to disable the overkill device by 0600 tomorrow
以阻止独立派的攻击
in order to prevent the separatist attack.
你们一给神盾局发信号
Once you signal S.H.I.E.L.D.,
救援小队就会马上带你们撤离
the extraction team will get you both out.
照顾好他
Take care of him.
是  长官
Of course, sir.
少说话多做事  沃德特工
More moving, less talking, Agent Ward.
我们时间可不多
Time's not on our side.
你觉得这样没问题吗
Does this feel okay to you?
我们不该跟他一起去吗
Shouldn't we be going with him?
参与本次行动的人员
The people who put these ops together
都是精英中的精英
are the best of the best.
他们很清楚自己在做什么
The know what they're doing.
高加索山
西蒙斯这会儿还什么都不知道呢
So Simmons, by this point, does not have a bloody clue.
我们在后面憋着笑
You know, we're in the back, trying to contain our laughter.
西蒙斯走进了真空室
So Simmons goes into the vacuum chamber wearing --
穿着兔子装
wearing a-a bunny suit.
我们这么叫是因为
Um, we just call it that because it
她全身都是
it covers your whole body.
她走进真空室
So she's in the vacuum chamber,
摘下面具要跟我说话
but when she takes her mask off to speak to me,
却把喷嚏都打在了法拉第杯上
she sneezes all over the Faraday cup...
多好笑
which is funny.
带信标了吗
Do you have the beacon?
带了
Yeah.
很好笑啊  因为真空室很干燥
But it's funny because vacuum chambers are so dry,
而这个仪器本来是要上太空的
and this instrument was actually supposed to go into space.
里面有高度灵敏的化学成分
It had sensitive chemical components.
西蒙斯说这故事效果比我要好得多
Simmons actually tells it a lot better than I do.
我的线人叫尤里・杜波斯基
Listen. My contact's Uri Dubrovsky.
我们付钱让他带我们过边境
We'll pay him to get us across the border.
我们认识很久了
We go back,
但他不喜欢新人
but he doesn't like new people,
所以闭嘴低头
so keep your mouth shut and your head down.
晚上好
两杯纯伏特加酒
一杯我的
一杯给我朋友尤里
能问问他们有什么现成的酒吗
Um, can you ask what beers that they have on tap?
尤里是你朋友吗
Uri is your friend?
是的
Yeah.
尤里已经死了
Uri's dead.
你在这里没朋友
You have no friends here.
别别别
Oh! No, no, no, no, no, no.
请小心点
Please be careful.
你能想象要是菲兹回来发现
Can you imagine what Fitz would do
他的"晚安  宝贝"坏了会干出什么事来吗
if the night-night gun was broken when he came back?
他出外勤会没事的  对吧
Surely he'll be okay out there, right?
梅特工有七级权限
Well, Agent May is level 7.
也许她能透露一点任务的消息给我们
Maybe she can give us an update on their mission.
你这样是说
Does that mean
你知情  但不能透露给我们
that you do know something and you can't tell us,
还是你也不知情
or that you don't know anything?
这样面无表情是什么意思
Which non-expression is this?
我们只要知道应该知道的
We know what we're supposed to.
有更多信息  我们就会作出反应
When we have more information, we'll react.
好了  清场
All right, clear out.
我要做些检查诊断  然后重启
I need to run some diagnostics, then reboot.
你俩也是  都出去
That means you two. Off.
也许你们可以容忍不明不白
You guys may be okay with being in the dark,
我可不行
but I'm not into it.
我要答案
I need answers.
而我知道谁有
And I know just the person who has them.
谁
Who?
科尔森
Coulson.
当然是科尔森
I'm obviously talking about coulson.
我还需要三支空降兵在边境待命
I'm going to need three more chalks queued up at the border.
第四支在亚美尼亚待命吗
And a fourth standing by in Armenia?
好主意
Great minds.
从那架飞机上下来感觉一定很好吧
It must be nice to be off that plane.
我知道你已经差不多康复了
I understand you're almost through your recovery.
那架飞机跟我的康复没有任何关系
The plane has nothing to do with my recovery.
我只知道档案里的信息
I only know what I've read.
弗瑞似乎对他喜欢的人很关照嘛
Seems Fury has a soft spot for his favorites.
不是所有人都会被送去塔希提岛
Not everyone gets sent to Tahiti.
那是个充满魔力的地方
It's a magical...place.
我的意思是回到大部队的感觉一定很好
All I meant was it must feel good to be back in the big leagues.
我的两个特工是这次行动的关键
Two of my agents are the key to this operation.
我从来没离开过大部队
I never left the bigs.
希望他们像你说的那么好
Let's hope they're as good as you think they are.
发生了什么事
What's happening?
为什么他们还不杀掉我们
Why haven't they killed us yet?
我是说  我很高兴他们还没杀掉我们
I mean, I'm glad that they haven't killed us yet.
他们在等他们的头儿
They're waiting for their boss,
他来之前  我们得做个计划
so before he gets here, we need a plan.
你能在水下屏气多长时间
How long can you hold your breath underwater?
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道"强棒出击"这个词吗
You familiar with the term "slam and cram"?
不  我也不想知道
No, and I d-- I don't think I want to be.
你的小指对你有多重要
How attached are you to your pinky?
非常非常重要  而且在你问出
Very, very attached, and before you ask
下一个吓死人的问题之前
another terrifyingly vague question,
让我把话说清楚
let me be clear.
任何需要牵扯到暴力的计划
Any plan that involves even one of those scenarios
对我都没用
isn't going to work for me.
实际上  我
As a matter of fact, I've --
听说你在找你的朋友尤里
I heard you were looking for your friend Uri.
尤里是分裂主义者的朋友
And Uri was friends with separatists.
你是分裂主义者吗
Are you separatists?
不
No.
我们是来阻止他们的
We're here to stop them.
绝对是来阻止他们的
Definitely here to stop them.
相信我
Trust me.
如果你能帮我们越过边境
If you could just help us get across the border --
真想回去看比赛
你在浪费我的时间  我把话说明吧
You're wasting my time, so let me be clear.
你没有给我信任你的理由
You've given me no reason to trust you.
信任对我来说就是一切
And trust is everything to me.
你好  很高兴在这里见到你
Hey. Fancy seeing you here.
斯凯
Skye,
我说过我会查你父母的档案的
I told you I'd look into the file about your parents.
我知道  我不是为那事儿来的
No, I know. That's not why I'm here.
我想知道更多关于沃德和菲兹的任务的事
I wanted to know more about Ward and Fitz's mission.
菲兹不在  西蒙斯已经快抓狂了
Simmons is seriously starting to unravel without Fitz.
我知道这话不好听
I know it's hard to hear,
但是你没有权限
but you don't have the clearance.
但我有眼睛啊
But I have eyes.
我看见六支全副武装的小队
I saw six squads in full tactical gear,
三箱火箭炮
three crates of RPGs,
还有一整队分析员指挥行动
and a full crew of analysts head to operations.
你真的打算告诉我
Are you really telling me
这些都跟沃德和菲兹的任务没关系吗
that has nothing to do with Ward and Fitz's mission?
如果我是对的
If I'm right,
你不用说话  给个信号就行
give me a signal by not saying anything.
要相信组织
Trust the system.
进展如何
How did it go?
一无所获
Nothing.
他现在就好像是个机器人一样
He's acting like a robot version of himself right now.
如果我们想知道真相
If we want the truth,
就得自己去找
we've got to get it ourselves.
好吧
Okay.
那你的建议是...
How would you suggest --
等等  不
Oh, wait. No. No.
-是的  -不
- Yes. - No!
我可不能成为你坏女孩恶作剧的一部分
I can't be a part of your bad-girl shenanigans.
我喜欢循规蹈矩  该做什么做什么
I like following the rules and doing what's expected of me.
这让我觉得安心
It makes me feel nice.
西蒙斯  醒醒吧
Simmons, wake up!
沃德和菲兹去执行绝密两人任务了
Ward and Fitz went on a top-secret, two-man operation,
而且你看
and look.
人越来越多
There are more men.
所以要么就是有什么大事件他们没告诉我们
And either it's a bigger deal and they're not telling us,
要么就是出什么问题了
or something went wrong out there.
也许我们帮不上什么忙
And maybe there's nothing we can to do help,
但如果能帮上忙  那就要先知情才行
but we got to know if there is.
万一他们受伤了或是正在被拷打怎么办
What if they're injured or being tortured somewhere right now?
菲兹
Fitz.
被严刑拷打
Tortured.
说说你的计划是什么
What exactly do you have in mind?
好了  够低了
Okay! Enough!
好吧
Okay.
稍微往左一点  弗拉基米尔
A little to the left, Vladimir.
慢点
Gentle!
Gentle.
就是这样  好了
That's it. Okay.
能再给我点照明吗  玛塔
Can I get a little more light down here, Marta?
当然  米什卡[俄语]
Of course, mishka.
谢谢你  亲爱的
Thank you, sweetheart.
你叫他熊宝宝
Little bear?
我喜欢看他干活的样子
I like watching him work,
那只熊宝宝
That little bear.
搞定了
Okay.
小事一桩
It's nothing.
真的
Really.
我只是个普通人而已
I'm just a man.
给这位普通人来杯酒
Get this man a drink.
不用了  好  喝就喝吧
Oh, no. Here we go.
咸咸的
Salty.
现在...
So...
我们来谈谈正事吧
Let's talk business.
你花了两百万卢布吗
Two million rubles?
看来你得好好学学谈判技巧了
We need to work on your negotiation skills.
我以为卢布跟比索一样不值钱
I thought they were like pesos.
再说了
And anyway,
你该感谢我
you should be thanking me.
在我们被绑着的时候是我用小型电磁脉冲
I shorted the fuse box with my localized E.M.P.
才让保险丝盒短路的
when we were tied up.
真的吗
Really?
没错  而我的计划也成功了
Yes, and my plan worked
现在我们不是越过边境了吗
Because we're over the border now, aren't we?
我们停下来了  为什么会停下来
We're stopping. Why are we stopping?
别出声
Quiet.
待在这里  我去看看什么情况
Stay here. I'll check it out.
好吧
Okay.
我们还是都先待着好了
Maybe we'll both stay here.
菲兹  更多边境巡逻的人来了
Fitz! More border patrol.
我已经开溜了  快跟上
Already moving! Hurry up!
抱歉  我打扰到你了吗
Sorry. Am I disturbing you?
知道吗  我喜欢这架飞机
You know, I like this plane.
我喜欢这里的工作方式
I like the way we do things here.
大家都对情况一样了解  没有机密
Everyone's on the same page, no red tape.
目前看来  这种方式挺适合我们的
So far, it's working for us.
至少对大部分人来说
Most of us.
或许我比以前优柔寡断了
And maybe I'm getting soft,
但我不喜欢对我们的队员有所隐瞒
But I don't like keeping things from our team.
如果你知道...
If you knew --
不  你是对的
No. You're right.
8级特权
Level 8.
但是...
But --
我懂的
I know.
相信组织
Trust the system.
梅
May?
谢谢你
Thanks.
笑一个
Say cheese.
准许进入  珍玛・西蒙斯
5级特工
闪存在你手上了  去吧
Okay, you have the flash drive. Go
我编写了一个伪装搜索程序
I programmed it with a decoy crawler.
它会用我的网页浏览记录
It'll use my browser history
来模拟我平时的上网活动
to simulate my usual online activity.
所以当神盾局以为我在用你给我的电脑
So while S.H.I.E.L.D thinks I'm trolling Reddit and Facebook
上无聊的社交网站时
with the laptop you gave me --
你其实正在偷取沃德和菲兹的任务文件
You'll be hacking the files for Ward and Fitz's mission.
没错
Right.
记住  一旦你插入闪存
And remember, once you plug it in,
你只有...
you'll only have about --
三分钟的时间不被神盾局察觉
Three minutes before S.H.I.E.L.D. catches on.
你发现了吗  你一直在接我的...
Do you realize that you keep finishing my sent--
你的句子  我知道
Your sentences. I know.
抱歉  我一紧张就这样
I'm sorry. Bad habit.
这还挺刺激的
This is actually a bit thrilling.
那真不错  你开心就好
Ah, good. I'm glad.
现在我们得想个法子把面板打开
Now we've just got to figure out a way to get the panel open.
别担心  我有特制工具
Don't worry. I made a special something.
我就是干这行的
It's what we do.
搞定了
All done.
真的吗  好厉害
Really? Wow. Okay.
现在只要找到一个USB插口就好
Uh, now just find a USB port.
好的
Okay.
西蒙斯特工
Agent Simmons?
没事  淡定
It's fine. Just play it cool.
你好  西特韦尔特工先生
Hello, Mr. Agent Sitwell, sir.
需要我帮忙吗
May I help you?
排污管
Drainage pipe.
我们在那里等他们出来
We'll wait them out over there.
我们不能等太久
We can't wait too long.
如果他们使用超强杀伤性武器
If they use the overkill device,
边境的所有人都有危险
everyone on the border's in danger.
我知道
I'm aware.
也包括玛塔和弗拉德
And that includes Marta and Vlad.
你跟他们已经熟到直呼其名了啊
Oh, you're on a first-name basis now?
我就是说
Yeah, well, I'm just saying,
他们现在也有生命危险
their lives are on the line, too,
所以我们还是别太安逸了
so let's not get too comfortable.
叫我贾斯珀
Call me Jasper.
这么晚了  什么风还把您吹到这机密走廊来了
What brings you to this restricted hallway so late at night?
我也想问你这个问题呢
I could ask you the same thing.
别  别问
No. Don't.
西蒙斯  专注  编个理由就可以了
Simmons, focus. Just make up an excuse.
我就是要去厕所
I was just on my way to the loo.
我敢肯定是右转右转再左转啊
I could swear it was two rights and a left,
但不在这里吗
but is that it here?
这是个墙面电脑板
That's a wall panel.
你摆弄这个干什么
Why are you accessing it?
别犹豫  说点什么  随便什么
Don't spiral. Just say something. Anything.
你脑袋长得真英俊啊
You certainly have a gorgeous head, don't you?
什么
What?
我就喜欢跟我差不多高
I like men that are about my height,
但是比我壮的男人
but heavier than me.
别说话了  停
Stop talking. Stop.
西蒙斯特工
Agent Simmons,
你有操作这个电脑板的许可吗
do you have authorization to access that panel?
说是的  说你有
Say yes. Say you do.
是...当然了
Y-- of course.
-很好  对  -当然了
- Great. Yeah. - Of course.
我肯定就放在我包里呢
Um, I certainly have it right here in my bag.
他盯上我了
He's onto me.
别跟我说话  他能听到
Stop talking to me! He can hear you!
你是在跟人通讯吗
Are you on comms with someone?
我是西特韦尔特工  我需要一名警卫
This is Agent Sitwell. I need an escort.
对不起
Aah! I'm sorry!
我的天呐  我的天呐
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
我干净利落地射晕了西特韦尔特工
I've definitely shot Agent Sitwell.
不错不错不错
Good, good, good.
刚才还好吧
Was that all right?
是非常糟糕
That was terrible.
你做这个实在弱爆了  那完全是个灾难
You are terrible at this. That was a total meltdown.
晚安枪就在这  我就...
The night-night gun was right there, and I
我们需要帮助  你得去找梅过来
We need help. You need to go get May.
梅  不要
May?! No!
听着
Listen.
闪存盘只能给我
That flash drive will only give me
几分钟时间访问中心的主机
a few minutes of access to the Hub's mainframe
查清我们的人发生了什么事
to find out what happened to our boys...
所以你快去找梅  好吗
...so just go get May, okay?
就跟她说这是个意外
Just tell her it was an accident.
我要上军事法庭了
I'm going to be court-martialed.
希望这个能成功
I hope this works.
你觉得神盾局为什么只派我们两个
Why do you think S.H.I.E.L.D. sent in just the two of us?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们说需要一个你这样的和一个我这样的
They said they needed a guy like you and a guy like me.
那是三明治吗
Is that a sandwich?
西蒙斯做的
Simmons made it.
我的最爱
My favorite.
熏火腿野牛肉和奶酪
Prosciutto and buffalo mozzarella
再加一点点蒜泥蛋黄酱
with a hint of pesto aioli.
给  可以分你一半
Here. You can have half.
搞什么鬼啊
What the hell?
有狗在追踪我们
There are dogs tracking us,
你还带个火腿三明治
and you bring a prosciutto sandwich.
真不敢相信你刚做了什么
I can't believe you just did that.
这是在执行任务  不是野餐
This is a mission, not a picnic.
我很清楚这不是野餐  救世主先生
Oh, I'm well aware it's not a picnic, Mr. Save the Day.
这话是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
拜托  你显然乐在其中
Oh, come on. You obviously get off on it,
做为一个常胜将军
being the guy who always gets to throw the last punch,
每次都能从天而降英雄救美
who always swoops in to save the girl.
现在你又摧毁了
And now you've destroyed
世上最危险的三明治
the world's most dangerous sandwich.
恭喜啊
Congratulations.
我跟你说
Well, I'll tell you something.
我不需要什么人救我  格兰特・沃德
I don't need to be rescued by anyone, Grant Ward.
-好...  -仔细听
- Yeah. - Oh, and listen.
我们出发前
Before we left,
科尔森让我照顾你
Coulson told me to take care of you.
所以我只负责照顾你  不多不少
That is what I am doing. Nothing more, nothing less.
给你
Here.
饿了的话先吃这个吧
If you're hungry, eat this.
是没有气味的
It's odorless.
好了
All right, boys.
来看看你们到底在哪里
Let's find out where you really are.
神盾局中枢主机
当前任务
已编辑文件
"Redacted documents."
好
Okay.
89.4.26
好
Okay.
找到了  要是能看到原始文件就好了
There it is...if I could just access the raw file.
糟了  时间不够了
Oh, crap. I don't have any time.
神盾局中枢主机
当前任务
南奥塞梯
神盾局任务
"赶尽杀绝"行动
南奥塞梯
军队地点
状态  两人小队
时刻表  8:00
营救计划  无
天哪
Oh, my God.
无营救计划
No extraction!
我是怎么跟你说的
What did I tell you?
你让我相信组织
You told me to trust the system.
可组织却让沃德和菲茨去送死
And the system sent Ward and Fitz in there to die.
这年头当老鼠真好
Good day to be a rat.
老鼠可以只管自己的事
I mean, there you are, minding your own business,
散播污秽和疾病  自己去找虫子吃
spreading filth and disease, scavenging for grub worms
或者是烂水果
or rotten fruit,
你瞧  突然就看到了
When lo and behold, you see it --
火腿牛肉奶酪三明治
a prosciutto and buffalo mozzarella sandwich...
菲茨
Fitz.
上面还有蒜泥蛋黄酱
...with just a hint of pesto aioli.
安静
Quiet.
感觉到了吗
Feel that?
是卡车
A truck.
马上过来了  快把袋子拉好
It's coming. Zip up the mag pouch.
我说过会帮你找你家人的信息的
I told you I'd get answers about your family.
我不是在找我家人的信息
That's not what I was looking for!
我是想看看
I was trying to find out
沃德和菲茨到底是去干什么了
what was happening with Ward and Fitz.
那是机密行动
That's a classified operation.
明明是自杀行动
It's a suicide mission!
我都看到了
I saw it all --
军队布置还有空袭安排
The troop placements, the aerial assault.
一旦沃德和菲茨解除装置
Once Ward and Fitz disable that device,
那里就会发动大规模进攻
there's going to be a huge attack on that compound,
但是没有营救计划  你却没跟我们说
with no extraction plan, and you hid that from us.
我没瞒你什么
I didn't hide anything from you.
你是没有权限了解详情
You don't have the clearance to know that.
神盾局就是这样吗
Is that really what S.H.I.E.L.D.'s all about?
八级权限者的命比五级权限的值钱
Level 5s are more expendable than level 8?
我们对你来说就只是数字吗
Is that all we are, just a number to you?
你说完了吗
Are you done?
我不知道  你说呢
I don't know. Am I?
如果神盾局没跟你说明
If s.H.I.E.L.D. keeps a secret from you,
那肯定是有原因的
it's for a good reason.
-秘密都只有自己知道吗  -不要打断我说话
- So they can hold all the secrets. - Don't interrupt.
你刚才黑进了八级权限的服务器
You just hacked a level-8 secure server,
看到了自己不该看的行动计划
saw operational plans that you have no context for.
如果一旦泄露
If details get out,
整个行动可能因此失败
the whole operation could be compromised,
会有人因此丧命  包括沃德和菲茨
lives could be lost, Ward and Fitz among them.
我知道  那两个人正是我们担心的
I know. Those are two people we care about.
在飞机上时  你一直跟我说
On the plane, you're always telling me
要跳出思维定势  所以我才违反规定
to think outside the box, so I went off book
因为我想帮他们留意着点保护他们
'cause I was trying to watch their backs.
我们的团队可以违反规定是因为有规定可循
Our team can go off book because there is a book.
一个中心
A hub.
一个可以作为坚强后盾的组织
An organization watching our backs.
你说你想成为其中的一员
You claim that you want to be a part of that,
成为一名神盾局的特工
a S.H.I.E.L.D. agent.
不是么
Do you?
是的
Yes.
因为未来的某一天
Because someday,
我可能会让你背负一个秘密
I may have to trust you with a secret,
但那之前我需要确定你可以保守那个秘密
and I need to know that you can keep it.
我可以问你个问题么
Can I ask you one question?
什么
What?
你知道根本没有沃德和菲兹的营救方案么
Did you know there was no extraction plan for Ward and Fitz?
这是机密信息
That's classified.
好了  快快
Okay. Go. Go. Go.
快  快  快
Go, go, go.
我来发撤离讯号
I'll signal extraction.
好的
Okay.
西蒙斯管这个叫"魔术窗"
Simmons calls it "The magic window."
你可能会问  这是X射线技术么
You'd probably guess, "Is that x-ray technology?"
实际上这张纸里嵌入了
There are actually s-band microwave antennae
S频段微波天线
embedded in this sheet.
工作原理更像是个雷达系统
Works more like a radar system, really.
好吧
Okay.
我们来看看
Let's see.
西边墙壁有两个守卫
Okay, we have two guards on the west wall.
两人都配备了自动武器
Both carrying automatic weapons.
纠正一下  是三个守卫
Correction. Make that three guards.
我们现在需要面对三个守卫了
We have three guards now.
天哪
Oh, my God.
天哪  沃德  那个人在袭击另两个人
Oh, my God, Ward. He's attacking the others.
他朝我们过来了
He's coming straight for us.
沃德
Ward.
Ward?!
快点  进来
Hurry. Inside.
现在我明白了
That makes sense now.
一定就是这个了
This must be it.
好怪
Weird.
内核一定在里面  那才是最重要的部分
Core must be inside here. That's what's important.
周围的这些管道只是为了增强和定位声音
The piping around it just serves to amplify and direct the sound,
以便远距离引爆炸药
to trigger munitions from a distance.
看起来不像是个能把飞机炸下来的东西
Doesn't look like it could take a jet out of the sky.
沃德特工  你现在你应该明白的
Well, you should know by now, Agent Ward,
人不可貌相
that looks can be deceiving.
好了么
Good?
好了
Yeah.
这可能要费点时间
This is gonna take a while.
给你十分钟
You have 10 minutes.
我以为你会说五分钟
I thought you'd say five.
西特韦尔特工现在在医务室
Agent Sitwell is in the infirmary.
很显然  你的一名队员
Apparently, a member of your team
把他给打晕了
rendered him unconscious.
只是个误会
A misunderstanding.
我会内部解决的
I'll handle the matter internally.
击晕一名特工不能算是误会
Tranquilizing an agent does not qualify as a misunderstanding.
你说得对
You're right.
但在没有营救小组的情况下
But being told there's an extraction team in place
却声称有
when, in fact, there isn't,
这就算误会了吧
that does.
我是八级权限
I'm level 8.
我有权知道关乎我小队安危的信息
I'm entitled to information regarding the welfare of my team.
你应该告诉我
You should have told me.
看来我用不着说了
Seemed I didn't have to.
知道了又能怎样呢  科尔森特工
And what would that have changed, Agent Coulson?
你自己也设计了很多这样的任务
You yourself have designed dozens of operations like this.
你知道这是什么情况
You know how this works.
通常我们都有个营救计划
Usually with an extraction plan.
巴顿[鹰眼]  罗曼诺夫[黑寡妇]
Barton, Romanoff --
他们从来没有营救计划
they never have an extraction plan.
但他们一开始就已经知道这种情况了
They know that going in.
菲兹特工根本没有实战经验
Agent Fitz is unproven in the field,
知道实情只会分散他的注意力和勇气
and knowing would have caused him to lose focus or courage.
那也应当由我来决定
That should have been my call.
我不确定你会答应
I wasn't sure you'd comply.
你的队伍里面包括一个带着电子号牌
Your team includes an electronically tagged non-agent
以走漏风声出名的非特工人员
who is notorious for leaking secrets,
这也提醒了我
which reminds me --
你是怎么得知这些信息的
how did you get this information again?
我知道一千人性命的价值
I know what the safety of a thousand men is worth.
我也知道销毁这个超强杀伤性武器的重要性
I know the importance of taking the overkill device out of play.
但我也了解我的人和他们的价值
But I also know my men and what they're worth!
参加与否应该由他们自己来决定
The decision to go in should have been theirs to make.
也许吧
Perhaps.
但是你要相信组织  科尔森特工
But you need to trust the system, Agent Coulson.
好了
All right.
告诉我使这玩意失效的最后步骤吧
Show me the final steps to disable this thing.
我会去搞定的
I'll get it done.
不  我们要坚持撤离方案
No, we stick to the extraction plan.
还有一分钟我就搞定了
I'll be done in a minute.
撤离方案搞砸了
The extraction plan's a bust.
说啥
What?
撤离部队没联系上
Exfil team didn't make contact.
一旦你把那东西拆了
Once you take that thing apart
我就发出远程信标  我们就只能靠自己了
and I set off the remote beacon, we're on our own.
你该走了
You should go.
我不走
I'm not leaving.
菲兹  没时间争论了
Fitz, there's no time to argue.
你认为我搞不定这些吗
You don't think I can't handle this?
不是  我只是想保护
No, I am trying to protect --
你认为我是个胆小鬼  是吧
Ah, you think I'm a coward. Is that it?
什么  当然不是
What? No.
我和你一样是一名神盾局特工
I am every bit the S.H.I.E.L.D. agent that you are.
你不必去证明给别人看
You don't have anything to prove.
你说我总是喜欢在最后时刻救人
What you said about me always needing to swoop in --
我知道换做是你  也会跳下飞机救西蒙斯
I know you would have jumped out of the plane to save Simmons,
她也知道这点
and she knows that, too.
我并不是想向任何人证明任何事
I'm not trying to prove anything to anyone.
好吗  在我们离开之前
Okay? Before we left, you're not the only one
科尔森也找过我
that Coulson talked to, okay?
他也叫我照顾你
He told me to take care of you, too.
这正是我要做的
And that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你明白吗
You understand?
而且我快饿死了
And I'm bloody starving.
你拿到情报了  我们要做出反应
You got the information. Now we react.
我们要去接我们的队员
We're gonna get our guys.
总得有人去做
Somebody has to.
那神盾局的袭击呢
What about the S.H.I.E.L.D. assault?
我们不会去干预
We won't interfere.
撤离行动不需要一个军营
You don't need a battalion for an extraction.
三人就能全身而退
Three can pull it off.
四个会更好
Four's better.
你来吗
You're in?
我以为我们要到八级权限才能讨论这件事
I thought we all had to be level 8 to discuss this.
我们什么也不讨论
We're not discussing anything.
菲兹  最后一次机会
Last chance, Fitz.
你确定你不想先撤退吗
Are you sure you don't want a head start?
因为在你扯掉最后一根电线那刻
Because the second you pull that final wire --
轮到你了
Your turn.
信标接通了  装置关闭了
Beacon's hot. The device is disabled.
开始行动
Mission's a go.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我们要在他们发现这装置关闭之前
We need to slip out of here before they notice
逃出去
the device is powered down.
明白
Got it.
我们需要一个新的计划
We need a new plan.
-你确定这能行吗  -能
- Are you sure this is gonna work? - Yes.
理论上来说
Theoretically.
拿着
Hold it.
好了  完成
Okay. Finished.
刚才那是怎么回事
What was that?
是神盾局
S.H.I.E.L.D.
他们已经开始攻击了
They've started their attack,
这意味着在他们炸毁基地之前
which means we don't have much time
我们的时间不多了
before they crush the compound.
爬到上面去  用这玩意
Get up there and take out
尽可能多地击落他们的武器
as many of their weapons as you can with that thing.
菲兹  就是现在
Fitz!
在你后面
Behind you!
我把他击晕了
I just did that.
好了  我们走吧
Okay. Let's go.
你说他们需要像你我这样的人是吗
You said they needed a guy like me and a guy like you, right?
是的
Right.
撤离部队来了
It's the extraction team!
来了更好的
Better.
是铁骑
It's the Cavalry.
就是喜欢看这种场面
Never get tired of seeing that.
科尔森的手下脱险了吗
Are Coulson's people clear?
脱险了
They are.
我没想到会有撤离行动
I thought there wasn't gonna be an extraction.
我们的所有人力需要用在别处
All our resources were needed elsewhere.
再说这是科尔森特工的队伍  他们不需要
And it's Agent Coulson's team. They didn't need one.
好了  去善后吧
Okay. Let's mop up.
谢谢来接应我们  长官
Thanks for coming to get us, sir.
我们自己人要照顾好自己人
We take care of our own.
干得好  菲兹
Well done, Fitz.
很高兴你安然无恙
So glad you're all right.
是啊
Yep.
再见到你也很高兴
Good to see you, too.
那个三明治...怎么样
The sandwich...how was it?
蒜泥蛋黄酱太多了吗
Too much aioli?
很美味
It was delicious.
曾经有那么一秒
You know, for a second there,
我还以为自己得找一个新监管人员了
I thought I'd have to find a new supervising officer.
抱歉让你失望了
Sorry to disappoint.
事实上  我被照顾得很好
Truth is, I was in good hands.
我一直在照看着沃德
I had Ward's back the whole time.
是啊
Yeah.
差不多把他从一伙俄罗斯暴徒手中救了出来
Pretty much saved him from a gang of Russian mobsters
还撂倒了几个家伙
and kicked a few guys' heads in.
不过关于任务的事情说得够多了
But enough mission talk already.
中心有什么激动人心的事情发生吗
Um, anything exciting happen at the Hub?
我向一位上级长官胸口开了一枪
I shot a superior officer in the chest.
我在想今天的事  我非常抱歉...
I was thinking about today, and I'm really sorry...
我只是想让你知道我没有忘记
I just wanted to let you know that I didn't forget
你在中心要求我的事情
about what you asked me back at the Hub.
什么意思
Uh, what do you mean?
关于你过去的未编辑档案
The un-redacted file about your past.
我找到了
I found it.
上面说了什么
Uh, w-what did it say?
文档不是直接关于你的
The document wasn't about you directly.
是关于把你
It was about the person
放在孤儿院的那个人的
who dropped you off at the orphanage.
结果发现那个人是一名神盾局特工
Turns out, it was a S.H.I.E.L.D. agent.
一名神盾局特工吗
A S.H.I.E.L.D. agent?
为什么  我是说  是谁  那是什么意思  我...
Why? I mean, who? What does that mean? I --
特工身分不明
The agent was unidentified.
我们不知道她是你的母亲
We don't know if she was your mother
还是只是在门口捡到了你
or if she just found you on a doorstep.
母亲
Mother?
是个女的吗
It was a woman?
我提交了进一步查看文件
I put in a request to dig further into the files
发掘一切相关材料的申请
for any related materials,
不过目前为止  我手上只有这么多
But right now, that's all I have.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉吗
Sorry?
是谢谢
Thank you.
非常感谢你
Thank you so much.
读完了吗
You finish reading it yet?
你跟她说了什么
What did you tell her?
真相
The truth.
我告诉她一名神盾局特工
I told her a S.H.I.E.L.D. agent
把她放在了孤儿院门口
dropped her off at the orphanage.
但是你没有告诉她原因
But you didn't tell her why.
我开不了口
I can't.
有些秘密注定要保守下去
Some secrets are meant to stay secret.
你会帮我查明到底发生了什么吗
Will you help me find out what really happened?
趟浑水啊
Dangerous waters.
不过我可以试试看
But I can try.
谢谢你
Thank you.
可怜的姑娘
Poor girl.
漫威《神盾局特工》
"Marvel's agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."
很快回来
will return in a moment.
公司总部
Company.
我需要访问一份受限文件
Yes, I need access to a restricted file.
编号BCY304604
Bravo charlie yankee 307604.
授权代码
Authorization code.
X2896
X-ray 2896.
您在寻找一份死亡和恢复报告对吗  长官
You're looking for a death and recovery report, sir?
是的  有关一名神盾局特工的
Yes, for a S.H.I.E.L.D. agent.
最感兴趣的是关于恢复部分的
Mostly interested in his recovery.
发生在塔希提岛
It took place in Tahiti.
我很抱歉  但您无权访问此文档  长官
I'm sorry, but you don't have access to that document, sir.
肯定是哪里弄错了  我有八级权限
There must be some mistake. I'm level 8.
我有权限访问那份文档
I have clearance for that file.
系统显示您没有
The system indicates you don't.
需要我向弗瑞局长提交一份正式申请吗  长官
Would you like me to submit a formal request to Director Fury, sir?
不必了  谢谢
No. Thank you.
------WebKitFormBoundarybxn1WJ8qI6HTNXTZ
Content-Disposition: form-data; name="mode"
formupload